Kelly, Matt, Papers /4222
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Matt Kelly Papers
1973-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kelly, Matt
/4222
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
8055324
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Nicole Dardia, June 20, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4217: ILR School Associate Dean's Office Files
Kelly, Matt
8055324
- Arbitration Cases, 1950-1974. (Box 1)
  - Arbitrations 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arbitrations 1969 - Sept, Oct, Aug, June, May, Feb (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nov, Aug, July, June, May 1970 Dec. 1969 Arbitrations, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arbitrations January - June 1971 Folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arbitrations January - June 1971 folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arbitrations July - December 1971 Folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arbitrations July - December 1971 Folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - January - June 1972 Arbitrations (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - July - December 1972 Arbitrations (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - January - June 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - July - December 1973 folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - July - December 1973 folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1974,1973, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kaiser Gypsum Co. Inc 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kaiser Gypsum Co. Inc. 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Kaiser Gypsum 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - St. John's Queens Hospital 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - St. John's Queens Hospital 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ST. John's Queens Hospital 11/7/74, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Stroehmann Brothers Company 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - NYS Dept. of Correctional Services 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - NYS Dept. of Correctional Services 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Arbitration Cases, 1974-1977. (Box 2)
  - Local 1199 Hospital Healthcare Employees folder 1 1991, 1982, 1977, 1978, 1974, 1984, 1974-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 1199 - Hospital Health Care Employees Folder 2, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1/1/74-7/1/74 Arbitration cases (7 public sector, 15 private) folder 1, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1/1/74 - 7/1/74 folder 2, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 7/1/74 - 12/31/74, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1976, 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1975, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kaiser Gypsum Company 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NYS Dept. of Correctional Services 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - St. John's Queen 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1/1/75-6/30/75 Arbitrations folder 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1/1/75 - 6/30/75 Arbitrations folder 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 7/1/75 - 12/31/75 Arbitrations folder 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 7/1/75 - 12/31/75 folder 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Utility Workers of America 1977, 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Utility Workers Union of America, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - January 1976 - June 1976 folder 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Jan 1976 - June 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1977 cases 61-66 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1978, 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1/1/77 - 6/30/77 Arbitrations, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 7/1/77 - 12/31/77 Arbitrations, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Arbitration Cases, 1978-1980. (Box 3)
  - Utility Workers of America 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Utility Workers of America 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1/1/78 - 6/30/78 Arbitrations, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 7/1/78 - 12/31/78, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 7/1/78 - 12/31/78 Arbitrations folder 2, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1984, 1985, 1983, 1979, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1980, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Port Authority of New York + New Jersey 1979-1988 folder 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Port Authority of New York + New Jersey 1979-1988 folder 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1/1/79 - 6/30/79 Arbitrations folder 2, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 7/1/79 - 12/31/79 Arbitrations folder 1, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - City of New York Dept. of Sanitation 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - City of New York 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1980, 1982, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 1/1/80 - 6/30/80 Arbitration cases folder 1, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1/1/80 - 6/30/80 folder 2, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - July - December 1980 Cases (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Chemical Bank 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Arbitration Cases, 1980-1984. (Box 4)
  - Drug Related ConED/ Local 1-2 Selected cases (1980-1987) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - North American Soccer League 1981-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Utility Workers of America 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - January - June 1981 cases (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - July - December 1981 cases (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1983, 1982, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - January - June 1982 Arbitration Cases (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Cases July 1982 - December 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1984, 1983, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1983, 1982, 1980, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Consolidated Edison 1983-1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Cases Jan - June 1983 folder 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Jan - June 1983 folder 2 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Jan - June 1983 folder 2 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Arbitrations July - Dec. 1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Arbitrations July - Dec. 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1987, 1984, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Consolidated Edison 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Jan. - June 1984 folder 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Jan - June 1984 Arbitrations folder 2 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Arbitration Cases, 1984-1987. (Box 5)
  - July - December 1984 folder 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - July - December 1984 folder 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Isabella Geriatric Center 11/8/85, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Isabella Geriatric Center 11/22/85, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1988, 1985, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1986-1985, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - January - June 1985 folder 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - January - June 1985 folder 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - July - December 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Isabella Geriatic Center 1986 folder 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Isabella Geriatric Center folder 2, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1988, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1987, 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Isabella Geriatric Center 3/27/86, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Isabella Geriatric Center 3/31/86, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - January - June 1986 folder 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Jan - June 1986 folder 2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - July - December 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Arbitration Cases, 1987-1989. (Box 6)
  - January - June 1987 folder 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - January - June 1987 folder 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1987 July - December Cases folder 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1987 July - December Cases folder 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1987 July - December Cases Folder 3 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1989, 1988, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - McCann Erickson 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Port Authority of New York + New Jersey 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Consolidated Edison Company 1973-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - January 1988 - June 1988 folder 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - January 1988 - June 1988 folder 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - January 1988 - June 1988 folder 3 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - January 1988 - June 1988 folder 3 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1988 July - December cases folder 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1988 July - December cases folder 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1988 July - December cases folder 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Public Service Electric + Gas (1991-1988), 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - January - July 1989 cases (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - July - December 1989 cases (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Port Authority of New York + New Jersey 1989/1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Arbitration Cases, 1989-1990. (Box 7)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1989, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1989, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Public Service Electric + Gas 1991, 1990, 1989, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Port authority of New York + New Jersey 8/23/89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Port authority of New York + New Jersey 6/21/89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Port authority of New York + New Jersey 6/27/89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Port authority of New York + New Jersey 7/21/89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Port authority of New York + New Jersey 8/17/89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Port authority of New York + New Jersey 8/25/89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Port authority of New York + New Jersey 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Port Authority of New York, New Jersey 1989, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Utility Workers of Union of America folder 1 (1991) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Utility Workers Union of America folder 4 (1991, 1990), 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Utility Workers Union of America folder 5 (1989) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Consolidated Edison 1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Con Ed Cases 418 - 419 1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Con Ed 420 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Terence Cardinal Cookie Health Care Center 1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Consolidated Edison Company of New York 1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Public Service Electric + Gas 11/3/90, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Port Authority of New York + New Jersey 3/1/90, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - British Airways 1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - January - June 1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 7/1/90 - 12/31/90 Arbitration Cases, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Arbitration Cases, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
  - Village of Tarrytown 1991/1990 folder 1, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Village of Tarrytown 1991/1990 folder 2, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Menorah Nursing Home 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Creative Works, Inc. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Our Lady of Mercy Medical Center Pelham Bay Division 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lionel Hampton Orchestra 1990/1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Greenwich Public Schools 1990/1991 folder 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Greenwich Public Schools 1990/1991 folder 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Town of Greenwich Board of Education 1990/1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Consolidated Edison Company Case 421 1990-1991 folder 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Con Ed 1990-91 folder 2, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Con Ed 423 1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Con Ed Case #436 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Con Ed Case #437 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Con Ed Case #438 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Con Ed Case #439 1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Con Ed Case #440 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Con Ed Case #441 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Con Ed Case #442 1991 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Con Ed Case #443 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Con Ed Case #444, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Con Ed Case #445, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Con Ed Case #446, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Con Ed Case #447 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Con Ed Case #447 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Con Ed Case #448 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Anheuser - Busch Distributors 1991 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - General Ceramics 1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - DynAir Services, Inc. 1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - New York University Medical Center 1991 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Town/Village of Harrison 1991 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Transworld Airlines 1991 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - 1/1/91 - 6/30/91 Arbitration Cases, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - 7/1/91 - 12/31/91 Arbitration Cases folder 1, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - 7/1/91 - 12/31/91 cases folder 2, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Arbitration Cases, 1992; Publications, 1936-1986. (Box 9)
  - 1/1/92 - 6/30/92 cases, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1992 folder 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Utility Workers Union of America 1992 folder 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Matthew A. Kelly Development+ Influence of the Municipal Power Plant in Holyoke City, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Matthew A. Kelly An inquiry into the Growth + Significance of the Exemption of Homesteads from Taxation, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Estimated Effect of Schedule of Rates Tentatively Proposed for Atlantic Coast Shipyards 29 Feb. 1944 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Matthew A. Kelly - Regulation of Hours of Labor of Federal Employees Including Employees of Public Contractors 1945 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Book Review - The Struggle for Democracy in Germany, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - German Cooperative Movement, M. Kelly, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Socialization of Germany Industry, M. Kelly, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Printers League Section 1965, 1966, 1964, 1963, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Analyses - Speeches - Printing Labor Relations 1969-1961, 1961-1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Collective Bargaining Monograph 1965 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Lithographers + Photoengravers International Union Handbook - 1968 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Lithographers + Photoengravers International Union - Background for Bargaining 1968 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Collective Bargaining Notes 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Collective Bargaining 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Articles + Clippings 1969-1984 folder 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Articles + Clippings folder 2 1969-1984 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Outlines 6/29/1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Unlabeled Monograph 1975 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Advance Reading - Writing the Collective Bargaining Agreement 1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Collective Bargaining + The Labor Contract - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration Manual, Part 1 - Meaning, Preparation, Procedures 1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Publications, n.d.. (Box 10)
  - An Analysis of the Provisions + The Economic Implications of the Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining 2, Kelly Text Chapters 9-12 Part 3, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Collective Bargaining 2 folder 2, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Collective Negotiations in the Public Sector, ND, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Contract Administration, ND, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Grievance/ Arbitration provisions + Seniority Provision, ND, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Deborah Persis Kelly - Resume, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - How to Win at the Bargaining table, ND (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Matthew Kelly Publications, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Printing as a Career, ND, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Printers League Workshop in Collective Bargaining (Outline), ND (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Printing Industry of America - Union Employers Section Labor Relations Manual, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - The Psychology of Collective Bargaining - Charles Rehmus (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Appendix - The Regulation of Hours of Labor of Federal Employees (Box 10, Folder 14)